http://www.bayportbank.com/privacy

Skip Navigation
Privacy
Swipe right to view the rest of the table.
Rev. 07/2018
FACTS
WHAT DOES FIRST STATE BANK AND TRUST DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Credit history
Account balances
Overdraft history
Payment history
Checking account information
When you are
no longer
our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons First State Bank and Trust chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does First State Bank and Trust share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For affiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
Questions?
Call 651.439.5195 or email us at info@fsbt.com
What We Do
How does First State Bank and Trust protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does First State Bank and Trust collect my personal information?
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
• Our affiliates include non-financial companies, such as Valley Agencies.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
• Nonaffiliates we share with include direct marketing companies.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
• Our joint marketing partners include, financial services companies and insurance companies.
Apply for a personal loan, mortgage, or deposit account.
Learn More
